Finding Aid for the James Arkatov Photographs PASC.0340.Coll-level-DAO
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Jazz Musicians, Series 1.
  - Tabackin, Lew, 1997 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Tapscott, Horace, 1996 December (Box 2)
  - Tapscott, Horace, 1996 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Tavaglioni, Steve, 1996; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 17)
    With Jeff Elliott.
  - Taylor, Cecil, 1997 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Taylor, Cecil, 1997 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Taylor, Cecil, 1997 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Taylor, Cecil, 1997 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Taylor, Cecil, 1997 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Terrasson, Jacky, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Terrasson, Jacky, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Thielemans, Toots, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Thielemans, Toots, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Thielemans, Toots, 1997 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Thielemans, Toots, 1997 May 14; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Thielemans, Toots, 1997 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Thielemans, Toots, 1997 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Thielemans, Toots, 1997 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Thielemans, Toots, 1997 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Thielemans, Toots, 1997 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Todd, Richard, 2000 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Todd, Richard, 2000 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Torme, Mel, 1996 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Torme, Mel, 1996 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Torme, Mel, 1996 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Turrentine, Stanley, 1998 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Unidentified, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Unidentified, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Unidentified Bassist, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Unidentified Bassist, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Unidentified Bassists, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Unidentified Group, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified Guitarist, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Unidentified Guitarist, 1997 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Unidentified Guitarist, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Unidentified Pianist, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Unidentified Pianist, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Unidentified Pianist, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
    binder 3 012
  - Unidentified Soprano Saxophone Player, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Unidentified Trio, 1999 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Vaché, Warren, 2001 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Viola, Al, 1986 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1, Folder 3)
    With Buddy Collette.
  - Viola, Al, 1986 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Walton, Cedar, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Walton, Cedar, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Walton, Cedar, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
    With Jackie McLean.
  - Walton, Cedar, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Walton, Cedar, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Warren Vaché and Harry Allen, 2001 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
    Vaché (trumpet); Allen (sax). Bassist unidentified.
  - Warren Vaché with Harry Allen, 2001 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
    With: unidentified bassist and unidentified pianist.
  - Watrous, Bill, 2000 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Watts, Ernie, 1996 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Watts, Ernie, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Watts, Ernie, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Watts, Ernie, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
    With Pete Christlieb and Rickey Woodward.
  - Watts, Ernie, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Watts, Ernie, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Watts, Ernie, 1996 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Watts, Ernie, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Watts, Ernie, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Wiggins, Gerald, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Wiggins, Gerald, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Wiggins, Gerald, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Wiggins, Gerald, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Williams, Claude "Fiddler", 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Williams, Claude "Fiddler", 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Wilson, Gerald, 1996 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Wilson, Gerald, 1996 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Wilson, Gerald, 1996 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
    With undentified person.
  - Wilson, Gerald, 1996 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Wilson, Gerald, 1996 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Wofford, Mike, 1996 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 16)
    With Bud Shank.
  - Woods, Phil, 1997 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Woodward, Rickey, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
    With Ernie Watts and Pete Christlieb.
  - Woodward, Rickey, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Woodward, Rickey, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Woodward, Rickey, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Zeitlin, Denny, 1997 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Fine Artists, Series 3.
  - Abakanowicz, Magdalenda, 1985; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
    Photograph taken in Los Angeles.
  - Acconci, Vito, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
    Photograph taken in New York City.
  - Albuquerque, Lita, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
    Photograph taken in Venice, CA.
  - Alexander, Hope, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    2 photographs. Photographs taken in New York City.
  - Alexander, John, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
  - Alexander, Peter, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    2 photographs. Photographs taken in Venice, CA.
  - Allen, Bill, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    2 photographs. Photographs taken in Los Angeles.
  - Alxander, Clytie, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    4 photographs. Photographs taken in Venice, CA.
  - Anderson, David, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    4 photographs. Photographs taken in Los Angeles.
  - Anderson, David, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Anderson, Laura, 1990; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Antonio, Julio, 1993; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Note
    1 Photograph taken in Los Angeles, Ca.
  - Appel, Karel, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    3 photographs. Photographs taken in Los Angeles.
  - Appel, Karel, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Arneson, Robert, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Arnoldi, Charles, 1988-1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Aronson, David, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Asher, Michael, 1990; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Bacerra, Ralph, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    2 photographs. Photographs taken in Pasadena, CA.
  - Bachardy, Don, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
  - Baldessari, John, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Baltz, Lewis, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Bates, David, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    2 photographs. Photographs taken in San Francisco.
  - Bechtle, Bob, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    4 photographs. Photographs taken in San Francisco.
  - Bell, Larry, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    4 photographs. Photographs taken in Arizona.
  - Bengston, Billy Al, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    5 photographs. Photographs taken in Los Angeles.
  - Benton, Fletcher, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Berland, Tony, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
  - Bermudez, Luis, 1990; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
  - Blackburn, Ed, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    2 photographs. Photographs taken in Texas.
  - Blackburn, Linda, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Bleckner, Ross, 1997; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Bleckner, Ross, 1997; 3.5 x 5.5 color photograph (Box 7)
  - Borofsky, Jonathan, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    5 photographs Photographs taken in Los Angeles.
  - Borofsky, Jonathan, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    6 photographs Photographs taken in Los Angeles.
  - Bravo, Manuel Alvarez, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    2 photographs Photographs taken in Los Angeles and New Mexico.
  - Brice, William, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Bristol, Horace, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    2 photographs Photographs taken in Los Angeles.
  - Brown, Chris, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Brown, Roger, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    4 photographs Photographs taken in Chicago.
  - Bungay, David, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Burden, Chris, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Burkhardt, Hans, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Burns, Marsha, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    2 photographs. Photographs taken in Seattle, WA.
  - Celmins, Vija, 1992 (Box 1)
    Celmins, Vija
  - Chamberlain, John, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Scope and Content
    2 Photographs taken in Los Angeles.
  - Chew, C.T., 1993; 8x10 b&w photographs (Box 6, Folder 11)
    General
    2 Photographs taken in Seattle, WA.
  - Chicago, Judy, 1992; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 11)
    3 Photographs taken in Los Angeles.
  - Chihuly, Dale, 1993; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 11)
    3 Photographs taken in Seattle, WA.
  - Close, Chuck, 1992; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 11)
    3 Photographs taken in New York City.
  - Coe, Sue, 1994; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Conal, Robbie, 1993; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 11)
    4 Photographs taken in Los Angeles.
  - Connell, John, 1992; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Conner, Bruce, 1992; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 12)
    4 Photographs taken in San Francisco, CA.
  - Cooper, Ron, 1992; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 12)
    3 Photographs taken in Taos, NM.
  - Cornelius, Phil, 1991; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 12)
    2 Photographs taken in Pasadena, CA.
  - Corse, Mary, 1991; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 12)
    2 Photographs taken in Los Angeles, CA.
  - Cuenca, Arturo, 1993; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 13)
    1 Photograph taken in Los Angeles, CA.
  - Cuevas, Jose Luis, 1989; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 12)
    3 photographs taken in Los Angeles, CA.
  - Creaman, Robert, 1994; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 12)
    3 Photographs taken in Los Angeles, CA.
  - Davis, Ron, 1992; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 13)
    1 Photograph taken in Taos, NM.
  - De Forest, Roy, 1991; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 13)
    3 Photographs taken in San Francisco.
  - DeLapp, Tony, 1991; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 13)
    2 Photographs taken in Los Angeles, Ca.
  - De Staebler, Steve, 1991; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 13)
    3 Photographs taken in San Francisco, CA.
  - De Szyszlo, 2007; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Diebenkorn, Richard, 1991; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 13)
    7 Photographs taken in Healdsburgh.
  - Dill, Guy, 1991; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Dill, Laddie John, 1990-1991; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 8, Folder 9)
    3 Photographs taken in Venice, CA.
  - Dillingham, Rick, 1992; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 8, Folder 9)
    3 Photographs taken in Santa Fe, NM.
  - Dine, Jim, 1992; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 8, Folder 9)
    4 Photographs taken in Los Angeles, CA.
  - Dingle, Kim, 1992; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Di Survero, Mark, 1991; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 8, Folder 9)
    4 Photographs taken in Orange County, Ca.
  - Dowell, Roy, 1991; 8x 10; b & w (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Eino, 1991-1993; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Eversley, Fred, 1993; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Felsen, Sid, 1999; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Fisher, Vernon, 1999; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Ford, Gordon Onslow, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 4)
    2 photographs. Photographs taken in Inverness, CA.
  - Foulkes, Llyn, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Francis, Sam, 1975; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Francis, Sam, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Frankenthaler, Helen, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Frasconi, Antonio, 1988; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Frey, Viola, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Ganzer, Jim, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Garabedian, Charles, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Garcia, Rupert, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Gehry, Frank, 1999; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 6)
    8 photographs. Photographs taken in Los Angeles.
  - Ginsberg, Allen, 1994; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Goode, Joe, 1989-1990; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 6)
    2 photographs. Photograph taken in Venice, CA.
  - Gorman, R.C., 1991-1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 6)
    5 photographs. Photographs taken in Taos, NM.
  - Gorman, R.C., 1992; 3 x 5 col. photograph (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Photograph taken in Taos, NM.
  - Graham, Robert, 1990-1993; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Grieger, Scott, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Also photographed: Alexis Smith.
  - Gronk, 1994; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Gummer, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Gunn, Thom, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Hauser, Alan, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 7)
  - Henderson, Mike, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Herman, Roger, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Herms, George, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Hockney, David, 1984-2006; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 8)
    16 photographs. Photographs taken in Los Angeles.
  - Holland, Tom, 1991 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 7)
    3 photographs. Photograph taken in San Francisco.
  - Holt, Nancy, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 7)
    2 photographs. Photograph taken in New York City.
  - Holzer, Jenny, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 7)
  - Holzer, Jenny, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Hopkins, Henry, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    2 photographs Photograph taken in Los Angeles
  - Hopper, Dennis, 1997; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Houser, Allan, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    3 photographs Photographs taken in Taos, NM.
  - Hudson, Bob, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 7)
    Photographs taken in San Francisco.
  - Hunt, Bryan, 1994; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    Photographs taken in New York City.
  - Irwin, Robert, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    Photographs taken in Los Angeles at the Getty.
  - Johns, Jasper, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w; color photoraphs (Box 7)
  - Kanemitsu, Matsumi, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    Photographs taken in Los Angeles. 2 photographs
  - Kauffman, Craig, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Kauffman, Craig, 1994; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Kelley, Mike, 1997; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 70)
    Photographs taken in Los Angeles. 6 photographs
  - Kelley, Robert, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    Photographs taken in Seattle, WA. 3 photographs
  - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    Photographs taken in New York City. 5 photographs
  - Kelly, Kenneth, 193; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    Photographs taken in New York City. 3 photographs
  - Kitaj, R.B., 194; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
  - Koons, Jeff, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    5 photographs. Photographs taken in San Francisco, CA.
  - Leslie, Alfred, 1994; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    6 photographs. Photographs taken in New York City.
  - Liebovitz, Annie, 1999; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Llosa, Mario Vargas, 1999; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Lobdell, Frank, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Lundeberg, Helen, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
  - Maki, Robert, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Maloof, Sam, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    3 photographs. Photographs taken in Pasadena, CA.
  - Maloof, Sam, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
    Photograph with wife, taken in Pasadena, CA.
  - Marden, Brice, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    3 photographs. Photographs taken in New York City.
  - Marquis, Richard, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Martin, Agnes, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
    2 photographs. Photographs taken in New Mexico.
  - Mason, Aldon, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Mason, John, 1992-1997; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - McCarthy, Paul, 1997; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - McLean, Richard, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Meier, Richard, 1994; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Milosz, Czeslaw, 1995; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Mitchell, Jeff, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Mizuno, Mineo, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Mulligan, Matt, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 8)
  - Nagle, Ron, 1988-1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Natzler, Otto, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Neri, Manuel, 1991-1993; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
    3 photographs. Photographs taken in San Francisco.
  - Newman, Eugene, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Newman, Eugene, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Noland, Ken, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
    4 photographs. Photographs taken in New York
  - Nutt, Jim, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
    Photographs taken in Chicago. 2 photographs.
  - Ocampo, Manuel, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
    2 photographs. Photograph taken in Los Angeles.
  - Okuluck, John, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Oldenburg, Claes, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
    Also in photograph: Coosje Van Bruggen.
    2 photographs. Photographs taken in New York.
  - Oldenburg, Claes, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 8)
    With John Baldassari.
  - Oliveira, Nathan, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Olmos, Edward James, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w photographs; color photograph (Box 8)
    2 b & w photographs. 1 color photograph. Photograph taken in Los Angeles.
  - Opie, Catherine, 1997; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
    3 photographs. Photograph taken in Los Angeles.
  - Orr, Eric, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Outterbridge, John, 1998; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Pardo, Jorge, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Parducci, Claudia, 1997; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
  - Parducci, Claudia, 1997; 3.5 x 5.5 color (Box 7)
    7 photographs.
  - Parhami, Julia, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 8)
  - Paschke, Ed, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Pettibon, Ray, 1998; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Phelan, Ellen, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8)
  - Pijoan, Irene, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Pittman, Lari, 1997; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Price, Ken, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Rady, Elsa, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Ramos, Mel, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    2 photographs. Photographs taken in Florida.
  - Ray, Charles, 1994; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Ribau, Marc, 1997; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
    Photograph taken in France.
  - Rivers, Larry, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Rockburne, Dorothea, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    4 photographs. Photographs taken in New York City.
  - Romero, Frank, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
  - Ruppersberg, Allen, 1997; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Ruscha, Ed, 1990; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Ruscha, Ed, 1990; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
    With Joe Goode.
  - Saar, Alison, 1993-1997; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Saar, Bettye, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Sarkisian, Paul, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Sarkisian, Paul, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Saunders, Raymond, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Saxe, Adrian, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Schmeisser, Jorg, 1989; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
    Photograph taken in Kyoto, Japan.
  - Schnabel, Julian, 1997; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Scholder, Fritz, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
  - Schulz, Cornelia, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Segal, George, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Serra, Richard, 1998; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Shapiro, Joel, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Shaw, Richard, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
    Photograph taken in Seattle, WA.
  - Shire, Peter, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
  - Siqueiros, David Alfaro, 1971; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    2 photographs. Photographs taken in Mexico.
  - Siqueiros, Mrs., 1971; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
    Photograph taken in Mexico.
  - Smith, Alexis, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    3 photographs. Photographs taken in Venice, CA.
  - Soldner, Paul, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    2 photographs. Photographs taken in Aspen, CO.
  - Sonnier, Keith, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Sperry, Ann, 1989; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    2 photographs Photographs taken in New York City.
  - Steir, Patricia, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Stevens, Craig, 1994; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
  - Suzuki, Goro, 1999; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Tamayo, Rufino, 1971-198; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    3 photographs. Photographs taken in Mexico.
  - Tamayo, Rufino, 1971; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
    With Salome Arkatov.
  - Tassananchalee, Komol, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 8)
  - Teske, Edmund, 1995; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Thiebaud, Wayne, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    2 photographs. Photographs taken in Sacramento, CA.
  - Thiebaud, Wayne, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Thornycroft, Ann, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    2 photographs. Photographs taken in Los Angeles, CA.
  - Tobias, Richard, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Treiman, Joyce, 1984; 8 x 8 b & w photograph (Box 7)
  - Treiman, Joyce, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
  - Tsatakawa, George, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    One photograph includes Gerald Tsatakawa.
    3 photographs. Photographs taken in Seattle, WA.
  - Tsutakaw, Gerard, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Turner, Robert, 1988; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Tuttle, Richard, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Valentine, DeWain, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Vallance, Jeffrey, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
  - Vandenberge, Peter, 1994; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Villa, Carlos, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    3 photographs. Photographs taken in Oakland, CA.
  - Villierme, Henry, 1994; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Viola, Bill, 1997; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Voulkos, Peter, 1997; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    6 photographs. Photographs taken in Oakland, Ca.
  - Voulkos, Peter, 1988; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
    Photograph taken in Oakland, CA.
  - Voulkos, Peter, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
  - Voulkos, Peter, 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    2 photographs. Photographs taken in Oakland, CA.
  - Wayne, June, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Wegman, William, 1992-1993; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Wesselman, Tom, 1992; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    3 photoraphs. Photographs taken in New York City.
  - Wiley, William, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)
    Photograph taken in San Francisco.
  - Wingo, Mike, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photograph (Box 7)